“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
MAN: Previously on The Originals.
- 你是克劳斯的父亲
- 你能让我复活
-You're Klaus' father?
-You can bring me back to life.
欢迎来到我的地狱
-(GASPS)
-Welcome to my hell.
你没事了
你是不是梦到我们父亲了？
You're all right.
Have you dreamt of our father?
- 我见到麦可了
- 我最近也经常梦到他
-I saw Mikael.
-I've been dreaming of him, too.
你母亲显然是个极有天赋的女巫
Your mother is clearly
a very gifted witch.
不管我怎么想
结局都是我和我的人会死
Any way I do the math,
it ends with me and my guys dead.
所以不管你和狼人在密谋着什么
So whatever it is you got coming
with the wolves,
你要知道，我会一直奋战到最后一刻
just know that I will fight
until I am dead!
干得漂亮
WOMAN: Nice job.
帮我省了亲自杀死这些吸血鬼的麻烦
You saved me the trouble
of killing all these vampires myself.
那个孩子有女巫的血统
That baby is part witch.
她必须先出生然后再死
She has to be born first
before she can die.
- 不要
- 只能这样了
-No!
-This is the way it had to be.
在给你众多的追求者之一写情书吗？
KLAUS: Writing a love letter
to one of your many suitors?
谁是那个幸运的收信者？
杰克森还是以利亚？
So who's the lucky recipient then.
Jackson or Elijah?
可别说是我
Don't tell me it's me.
我以为我早就出局了呢
I thought I was out of the running
ages ago.
最自大狂奖项要颁给…
The award for biggest ego goes to....
我们的狼宝宝还好吗？
How is our littlest wolf?
你想不想…
Do you want to....
来吧
Come on.
你感觉到了吗？
-(GASPS)
-(LAUGHS) Feel that?
好吧
Right.
我就不打扰你写信了
I'll leave you
to your secret letter then.
亲爱的柔伊
HAYLEY: Dear Zoey.
凯特琳，或是安琪拉
Or Caitlin or Angela.
我亲爱的女儿
To my little girl...
你父亲刚问我这是不是一封情书
your dad just asked
if this was a love letter. (CHUCKLES)
我想也算是吧
I guess it kind of is.
我没有机会认识我母亲
HAYLEY: I never got
to know my mother.
所以我也不知道她怀着我时是什么心情
I have no idea what she must have
felt when she carried me.
放开我，你这贱人！
Let go of me, you bitch!
所以我想写这封信给你
HAYLEY: So I thought
I'd write to you
好让你知道此刻我有多么开心
so that you could know how happy
I am at this very moment.
我和你父亲都迫不及待想见到你
How much your father and I
can't wait to meet you.
我还想向你保证
And I want to make you a promise,
三样我从未有拥有过的东西
three things that you will have
that I never did.
一个安全的家
A safe home,
有人每天说爱你
someone to tell you
that they love you every single day
并且无条件守护着你
and someone to fight for you
no matter what.
换句话说，一个家
HAYLEY: In other words, a family.
就这样了，宝贝女儿
So there you go, baby girl.
其他的就让我们以后一起共同努力吧
The rest we're going to
have to figure out together.
我爱你，妈妈
I love you. Your mom.
你要知道这么做我也很痛苦
You should know
this brings me no joy.
我保证会速战速决的
-I promise I'll make it quick.
-(SCREAMlNG)
我们开始吧
Let's begin, shall we?
不，不要
No, no, no!
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：生死循环
主演：约瑟夫摩根
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
主演：菲比托金
卡密
Cami?
天啊
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
Oh, God. What happened?
- 出什么事了？
- 克劳斯
-Klaus.
他们大战了一场，他被咬了
主演：莉雅派普斯
-They fought, and he got bit.
- 马赛尔
- 没事的
-Marcel.
-It's okay.
他也没比我好多少
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
I gave as good as I got,
但我们需要克劳斯的血才能治愈
but we need Klaus's blood to heal.
你和克劳斯交手
You fought Klaus.
- 他流血了吗？
- 我确实将他伤得不轻
-Did he bleed?
-I got him pretty good, yeah.
在哪里？
Where?
黛维娜
Uh, Davina.
你在干什么？
What the hell?
小约，你来这里干什么？
Josh, what are you doing here?
我不是叫你好好休息吗？
制片：克里斯多福贺利尔
I told you to rest.
我没事
制片：克里斯多福贺利尔
-I'm fine.
你很快就会产生幻觉了
-You're going to start hallucinating soon.
除非我的幻觉就是
制片：兰斯安德森
I mean, unless I'm hallucinating you
你莫名其妙站在马路中央，念着咒语
standing in the middle of the street
and chanting for no reason. (LAUGHS)
等等，这真的是幻觉吗？
Wait. Am l?
我会救你的
我会救你们所有人
I'm going to save you.
I'm going to save all of you.
制片：邦妮怀斯
编剧：黛安艾德穆强
好吧
导演：麦特海斯廷
Okay.
看来我产生幻觉了
I am hallucinating.
- 你们都不得好死
- 再用力，宝宝快出来了
-I will bring hell to your doorstep!
-One last push. Baby's almost here.
我要用你们的鲜血沐浴
I will bathe
in rivers of your blood.
- 我看到宝宝了
- 好了，现在用力
-I can see the baby.
-Okay, now push.
- 慢慢来，慢慢来
- 你们都将尖叫着死去
-Gently, gently.
-You will die screaming!
好了
There.
是个漂亮的小女孩
You have a beautiful baby daughter.
清晨月亮落下时
We must start the sacrifice
我们就必须开始献祭
as soon as the moon sets
with the morning sky.
求求你
Please.
能让我抱抱她吗？
Please, can I hold her?
不！
No!
海莉
Hayley!
不
No.
她死了
She's gone.
你被咬了
KLAUS: You've been bitten.
这些只够一个人喝
There's only enough here for one.
不，一定够的
No. This has to be enough.
我没法选择
I can't choose.
求求你别逼我做选择
Please don't make me choose.
去救你的朋友吧
Save your friend.
我来照顾其他人
I can take care of the rest of us.
- 马赛尔
- 我不要
-Marcel.
-I can't.
看看你的伤口
你没时间废话了
Judging by the look of that bite,
you don't have time to argue.
马赛尔
Marcel.
小约是我的人
Josh is one of my guys.
今天我的人死得够多了
快喝吧
Enough of my guys have died today,
so come on.
你得一分
One point for you...
尼克劳斯也得一分
and one point for Niklaus. (ECHOlNG)
嘿
你要去哪？
Hey.
Where do you think you're going?
去找克劳斯，拿他的血
尽全力救我的手下
To find Klaus, get his blood, and
save as many of my guys as I can.
等等
Wait.
这样的话，你需要武器
For that, you'll need a weapon.
正好我有个武器库
And it just so happens
I have an arsenal.
- 怎么会这样？
- 我被打败了
-How?
-I was bested.
你被打败了？
You were bested?
你…
居然会被打败！
You were bested!
我战无不胜的弟弟
My invincible brother.
她们带走了孩子，但还有时间
They took the baby
but there's still time.
我们可以救她
We can save her.
墓地都空了，这地方都荒废了
她不在这里
Tombs are empty, the grounds
are deserted. She's not here!
她们只可能来这
我们要继续找
This is the only place they can be.
We'll keep searching.
她们不在这里，尼克劳斯
我们在浪费时间
They are not here, Niklaus.
We're wasting time!
她们的收获仪式在这里
收割仪式也在这里
Their harvest was here,
the reaping was here.
她们现在就要举行仪式
去祭祀她们的祖先
They are about to perform a ritual which
will feed their ancestors for centuries,
而她们的祖先就是埋在这里的
ancestors who are buried here.
这个雕像
This statue.
我们已经路过它三次了
我们一直都是朝同一个方向走
We've passed by this three times, all
whilst going in the same direction.
她们一定施了某种幻觉咒语了
They have fabricated
some kind of illusion.
看来你说得没错
That's one word for it.
- 这就是基兰隐藏的东西
- 说储藏更确切点
-So this is what Kieran was hiding.
-More like stockpiling.
我看了一下，基本上都是些武器
From what I can gather,
it's mostly weapons.
都是女巫制造出来的黑暗魔物
Dark objects created by witches.
被人类所借用
And co-opted by the humans.
基兰多年来一直守着这个秘密
Kieran's been keeping this
a secret for years.
你确定要给我看这些东西吗？
You sure you want to show me all this?
你说过得知我叔叔的秘密会害我丧命
You said knowing my uncle's secrets
could get me killed.
但要是这些秘密能拯救我的朋友呢？
But what if those same secrets
could save the lives of my friends?
看这个
我在学校里学过
Look at this.
I learned about it in the Lycee.
它叫做恶魔之星
It's called the Devil's Star.
据说投掷一次就能造成一千道伤口
They say one throw
can make a thousand cuts.
一千道伤口听起来不错
我就是要让克劳斯流血
A thousand cuts sounds about right.
I need to make Klaus bleed.
这东西太妙了
It's ingenious.
我看得见它们，也感觉得到它们
但它们并不存在
I can see them, I can feel them,
and yet they are not real.
一定有办法
There has to be a way.
- 要是能直接离开这里就好了
- 我们需要集中精力
-Even if we could just push through--
-What we need to do is focus.
我现在唯一关心的就是孩子和她的安危
My only focus right now is that child
and her safety.
你懂吗？
Do you understand me?
这一切
This, all of this.
这一切就是你创造的世界，尼克劳斯
This is the world
that you created, Niklaus.
- 哥哥
- 你的那些阴谋
-Brother--
-All of your scheming,
你可悲的一生每天都在树敌
the enemies that you have made
every day of your miserable life.
你还指望有什么结果？
What results did you expect?
你难道觉得你的孩子能过着幸福的生活
That your child would be born
into a happy life?
而她的母亲可以好好活着
看着她长大吗？
That the mother would be alive
to know her daughter?
亦或我们可以像普通家庭一样
安定地生活？
That we could live and thrive
as some sort of family?
- 那是你的幻想，不是我的！
- 不！弟弟。
这曾是我们的希望
This was our hope.
是我们家的希望
This was our family's hope.
但现在她不在了
And now she is gone.
你明白吗？
我让她进入了我的生活
Do you understand?
I let this person in.
我接纳了她
I let her in.
我从不接纳任何人的
I don't let people in.
你明知道这一点
却还是将她从我身边夺走
You knew this,
and you've taken her from me.
我需要她，而你毁了我
I needed her,
and you've broken me.
等我们救下你侄女
You can tell your niece
你可以告诉她
你有多在乎她母亲
how much you cared for her mother
when we save her.
用力
Push.
不！
No!
天快亮了，月亮差不多隐没了
The moon has almost faded
from the morning sky.
我得做好准备
I need to prepare.
她一定会进行到底
祖先们已保证她会活下去
She'll go through with it.
The ancestors promised her her life.
那他们对我们的保证呢？
What about their promise to us?
收获祭上四个女孩牺牲，四个女孩复活
Four harvest girls sacrificed,
four girls returned.
但她的朋友破坏了一切
我们的朋友就不能复活了吗？
But her friends hijack it,
and ours have to stay dead?
凯西是我们的朋友
Cassie was our friend.
我希望她进行不下去
I hope she doesn't go through
with it.
然后由我们来完成祖先的愿望
Then you and l
can do what the ancestors want,
他们就会把凯西还给我们
and they'll give us Cassie.
洁妮薇就可以回到她该去的地方了
And drag Genevieve
back to where she came from.
是时候了
It's time.
上面说我必须从连结漩涡中获取能量
It says I need to channel power
from a Nexus Vorti.
是啊
(LAUGHS) Ah, yes.
我妻子艾丝塔总是喜欢夸张一点的说法
My wife, Esther, always did love
to dress things up a bit.
只是女巫的说法而已
It's fancy witch speak.
连结漩涡，一种很罕见的现象
Nexus Vorti.
A rare occurrence.
极其罕见
甚至可以说是奇迹
Something so infrequent,
it's almost a miracle
比如占星术中的事件，或是…
Iike an astrological event, or...
- 一个奇迹般的孩子
- 没错
-A miracle baby.
- Voila.
你确定你有能力让我复活吗？
Are you certain you have the power
to bring me back?
我现在有了
I do now.
我们是第二次经过这里了
We've passed through here
twice already.
快没时间了
-We're running out of time.
-(CLATTERlNG)
那就动作快点
Then we move faster.
或更聪明点
HAYLEY: Or smarter.
海莉
Hayley.
你怎么会来这里？
How are you here?
我在教堂里醒来
我感觉到饥饿
I woke up in the church.
I felt this hunger.
我知道我需要什么
I knew what I needed.
我感觉得到她
I can feel her.
她就在这里
She's here.
我感觉得到我的孩子
I can feel my baby.
你死的时候，孩子的血还在你体内
You died with the baby's blood
still in your system.
她正在转变
She's in transition.
也就是说，她要想活命
必须喝孩子的血
Which means she has to drink the
blood of the child if she's to survive.
这样才能成为混合种
To be a reborn hybrid.
我不在乎自己
I don't care about me.
我要去找我们的女儿
I'm going to go find our daughter.
尘灰成骨
骨肉重组
From ash to bone,
from bone to flesh,
魂归人间
from flesh to life.
不！
No!
你们这群傻瓜
You fools!
在我们最强大的时候
来到我们能量的聚集地
To come against us
in our place of power,
与我们作对
in our strongest hour.
你们面对的不是三个人
You don't face three.
是我们所有人
You face us all.
你是谁？
MAN: Who the hell are you?
不！
No! (SCREAMS)
No!
我来晚了
I was too late.
应该可以有更多时间的
There should have been more time.
看来狼人们回来把事情做了个了结
Looks like the wolves came back
and finished what they started.
你抢走我女儿
就为了让我治愈你和你朋友
You took my daughter so l
would heal you and your friends.
来
Here.
这个咬伤
This bite.
所有的这一切
All this.
我知道不是没有原因的
I know it didn't come from nowhere.
一个世纪前，我把你父亲引来这里
开始了这一切
This is the last note in a song
that I started a century ago.
如今到了结局之时
When I brought your dad to town.
为此，我很抱歉
And for that, I am sorry.
不
No.
你救了我孩子的命，马赛尔
You saved my child's life, Marcel.
因此
这是你应得的
For that, you deserve this.
我们会打倒
造成这一切的罪魁祸首
We will take down
whoever brought this upon us.
我发誓
I swear it.
能让我抱抱吗？
May l?
嘿
Hey.
你好啊
Hey there.
- 住手
- 不
-Stop! Ah!
-No.
为什么会这样？
Why is this happening?
你复活我是为了杀我儿子
You brought me back to kill my son.
我复活你是为了惩罚他
I brought you back to punish him.
等我准备好了你自然会有机会
And you will when I'm ready
and not a minute before.
你到底做了什么？
What have you done?
我在你的复活咒语里加了点别的东西
I added a little something extra
in the spell that brought you back.
我耗费了八个月的生命
待在这当秘密武器
I spent eight months of my life here
being used as a secret weapon.
现在你也能体会一下这感受
Now you can see how it feels.
跪下
Kneel.
为什么？
Why?
祖先们没有给我选择的余地
The ancestors left me no choice.
你想牺牲一个无辜的婴儿
以获得更多力量
You were willing to sacrifice
an innocent baby for more power.
不只是力量
Oh, not just power.
那是祖先的决定
It was the ancestors' decree.
是她的决定
It was her decree.
谁的决定？
It was whose decree?
我很惊讶你会这么问
I'm surprised you have to ask.
毕竟正是你说服了你的弟弟妹妹
After all, you were the one
who convinced your siblings
在纽奥良的土地上将她献祭
to consecrate her
in New Orleans soil.
艾丝塔
Esther.
所以即便死亡也无法阻止我母亲
灭绝她亲骨肉的决心
So not even death can stop my mother
from seeking the annihilation
of her own flesh and blood.
这并不是终结
This isn't the end.
只要那个孩子还活着
As long as that child lives,
纽奥良的女巫就不会停止追杀她
the witches of New Orleans
will never stop coming for it.
艾丝塔永远不会停止追杀她
Esther will never stop
coming for it.
一切都已经决定了
It has been decreed.
你的孩子将被献祭给祖先们
Your baby will be consecrated
among her ancestors.
她活不了的
She will not live.
他们也来找我了
我能感觉到
They're coming for me.
I can feel it.
我让他们失望了
I've failed them.
求求你们
Please.
请理解，我只是想活下去
Understand, I just wanted to live.
告诉克劳斯
我很抱歉
Tell Klaus I'm sorry.
我可不
I'm not.
（杜曼街）
我们早该察觉母亲与这事有关的
We should have felt
our mother's hand in this.
我们早该知道
We should have known
she would not be bound
死亡也无法阻止她的
by anything as obvious as death.
如今她控制了女巫
and now she has control
of the witches.
- 她们不会停手的
- 对
-They will never stop.
-No.
葛雷拉家族也不会善罢甘休的
Nor would I expect
the Guerrera Wolves to back down.
海莉和孩子是狼人中的皇室
Hayley and the child
are wolf royalty.
因此她们对佛朗西丝卡的统治
就是一种威胁
And as such, they are a threat
to Francesca's claim to leadership.
她们永远不会安全的
They will never be safe.
你之前对我怎么说的
What was it you said to me earlier,
我可悲的一生每天都在树敌？
that I've made enemies
every day of my miserable life?
最可怕的敌人就在我们身边，哥哥
Well, the worst of them
are within these borders, brother.
我为世界带来了一个可以对付我的武器
I have brought into the world
a weapon they can use against me.
那我们就武装好自己
ELlJAH: Then we will arm ourselves.
弟弟，我们已经和这里每一个对手
交手过，我们都赢了
Brother, we fought every adversary
in this town and we have won.
不论对手是谁
我们会再次和他们交手
We'll fight them again,
no matter who they are.
我们要把这个家变成坚实的堡垒
We'll make this home a fortress.
我不会让她过囚犯一样的生活
I will not have her live her life
as a prisoner.
那就离开这里，我们一起走
Then we leave here together,
all of us.
无论我们去哪
无论逃到多远
Wherever we go, however far we run,
那些追求权力和复仇的人会一直
追杀我们，也会追杀她
those who seek power and revenge
will hunt us. They will hunt her.
我们的敌人都成了她的敌人
她却没有我们的抵抗能力
She has inherited all our enemies
with none of our defenses.
所以不论我们是留下还是离开
她都备受威胁
So whether we stay or we leave,
we condemn her.
还有第三个选择
HAYLEY: There is a third option.
我在战争的环境中长大
I grew up in a war zone.
我父母以为他们能保护我
My parents thought
they could protect me.
但最终，他们被屠杀了
But in the end,
they were slaughtered,
我的童年孤独无依，没人疼爱
and I spent my childhood alone
and unloved.
我对宝宝也对自己发誓
I made a promise to my baby
and to myself.
她的童年不会像我一样
That she would not grow up
like I did.
她会在安全有爱的环境下长大
That she would grow up
safe and loved.
然而她来到这世上的第一天
And yet here she is
on her first day in this world
祖母就想将她献祭
with a grandmother
that is bent on sacrificing her.
母亲则不得不喝她的血
And a mother that has to drink
the blood of her own baby
才能变成泥合种活下来
to survive transitioning
into a hybrid.
我是最爱她的人
And I'm the one
that loves her the most.
我想我们唯一能做的事
就是送走她
I think the only thing to do
is send her away
我们自己留下来
while we stay behind
收拾好我们制造的烂摊子
and clean up the mess
that we've made.
不，这太疯狂了
No. This is insane.
你听到洁妮薇说的话了
You heard Genevieve.
只要这孩子活着，她就会一直被追杀
So long as she lives,
that baby will be hunted.
如果没人知道她还活着呢？
What if no one knows she lives?
你想要干什么，弟弟？
What is it that you intend to do,
brother?
不惜一切代价
拯救我们的家人
Whatever it takes
to save our family.
今天是法语区全新的开始
Today begins a new day
in the quarter.
我长久以来居住在这里的家人
My family, long-time residents
of this great community,
许诺会帮助每一位市民
pledges to help every citizen
从昨晚在我们街头所爆发的
recover from the terrible outbreak
of gang violence
可怕的帮派暴力冲突中恢复过来
that erupted on the streets
of our city last night.
我们将重建城市
We will rebuild.
我们会记住那些逝去的人
We will remember those who perished
我们要努力消除这个城市里的毒瘤
as we seek to disinfect this town
of its worst elements.
我们会一起努力
We will work together
保证“新月城”纽奥良市
再次繁荣
to ensure the heart
of the Crescent City thrives again.
坚持到最后的人
Last man standing, huh?
我想做个交易
I'm interested in making a deal.
看起来你也没什么可给的
Don't look like
you got much to offer.
我听说葛雷拉家族想要让法语区
变成没有吸血鬼的地方
I'm hearing word that the Guerreras
want the quarter to be a no vampire zone.
我能做到这点
I can make that happen
交换是，你们不要再干涉
住在河对岸的我们
in exchange for you leaving us alone
across the river.
否则我会给你们的新狼群带来痛苦
Or I can unleash hell
on your new wolf pack.
- 你要怎么做？
- 简单
-And how can you do that?
-Easy.
我和克劳斯讲和了
他治愈了我
I made my peace with Klaus.
He cured me.
现在是你们和我们对抗
So now it's you versus us.
克劳斯…
是个好战者
Klaus is a warmonger.
你觉得他会选择站在
You think he's gonna choose to side
一群瘦弱的吸血鬼那边
with a pack of scrawny vamps...
还是他创造的新狼族大军这边呢？
...or an army of the new wolf breed
that he created?
我想他会站在我们这边的
I'm thinking
he's gonna side with us.
尤其是当他发现
你们的族人杀死了他的孩子
Especially after he finds out
that your pack killed his kid.
什么？
What?
打开箱子
Open the box,
告诉我你觉得克劳斯会认为
and let me know
what you think Klaus will believe
谁该为箱子里的东西负责
about who's responsible
for what you find inside of it.
火化也许是最好的方式
趁克劳斯还没追查到你之前
Cremation may be the best way to go
before Klaus smells it on you.
（我们想你）
（悼念米卡森宝宝）
克劳斯
CAMl: Klaus.
孩子？
The baby?
她死了
She died.
在葛雷拉发动攻击几小时之后
A few hours
after the Guerrera attack.
这…
这都是我的错
This is--
This is all my fault.
- 我向你保证，不是你的错
- 不
-I can assure you it is not.
-No.
如果我没有迟疑
If I hadn't hesitated,
我就能及时揭穿佛朗西丝卡的阴谋
阻止这一切
I could have uncovered
Francesca's plot in time to stop it.
那你要如何阻止女巫与她联手？
And how would you have stopped the
coven of witches in league with her?
不
No.
如果要怪谁，一定是我
If anyone is to blame, I am.
我真的很抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
卡蜜儿
Camille.
我感谢你能来这里
但我们不能成为朋友
I appreciate you being here,
but we cannot be friends.
什么？
What?
你一开始就说对了
You had me pegged from the start.
我被自己的恶魔摧毁了
那些恶魔还在纠缠不休
A man damaged by his demons,
and those demons are not dormant.
他们下定决心要杀死我
还有我眼里美好的一切
They are hell-bent on killing me
and everything I find beautiful.
而你
And you.
你那么美好
You are beautiful.
求求你
Please.
- 求你走吧
- 克劳斯
-Please just go.
-Klaus.
走吧
Go.
马赛尔的任务完成了吗？
Did Marcel play his part?
他在路易斯安那州北部的一家医院里
He managed
to locate a stillborn baby
找到了一个胎死腹中的孩子
in a hospital in upstate Louisiana.
我想他是接受我们的条件了
I trust he agreed to the terms.
他同意让我魅惑他
He has agreed
to allow me to compel him
忘记我孩子的事情
to forget what he knows of my child.
交换是，他要几小瓶我的血液
In exchange,
he wants vials of my blood.
必须让女巫相信才行
But the witches
will have to believe this.
第四名收获祭女孩很快就会复活
Soon that fourth harvest girl
will resurrect.
女巫又将复原
The coven will rebuild.
要是她们察觉你的孩子还活着
她们会追杀她的
If they sense that your child lives,
they will hunt her.
女巫们会相信我们说的话
The witches will buy what we sell.
只要我们能自圆其说
We just have to sell it properly.
那就只剩下道别了
Well, then all that remains
is to say goodbye.
他们会看着我们
所有人
KLAUS: They will be watching us,
all of them.
我们三人一起离开会引来许多注意
The three of us leaving together
will draw too much attention.
我会独自离开
I will go alone.
我走了之后，你们要参加公众追悼会
Take your mourning public
when I'm gone.
我想那不会太难的
I don't imagine
that will be too difficult.
毕竟，悲伤的情绪是真的
Grief, after all, is grief.
离开我们她要在哪才会安全，弟弟？
ELlJAH: In what world will she
be safe without us, brother?
谁能比我们提供更好的保护给她？
Who can protect her better than we?
有一个人能
KLAUS: There is one person.
你好，妹妹
Hello, sister.
她长得像她妈妈
Oh, she looks like her mother.
也许真的有上帝
Maybe there is a God after all.
她的眼里看得到些许恶魔的影子
Well, she has a hint of the devil
in her eyes.
那是遗传我的
That's all me.
你需要一个可以信赖的女巫
施个隐身咒
You'll need a witch you can trust
to cast a cloaking spell.
我会找到的
I'll get one.
- 不能让任何人发现她
- 我知道该怎么做，尼克
-No one can ever find her.
-I know what to do, Nik.
也许我们会建起白色的篱笆
我想那一定会很美
Perhaps we'll get a white fence.
I think that would be lovely.
这个城市以为你死了
This city would have seen you dead,
但我会把这里变成你的家
but I will have it your home.
每一个想要伤害你的人
都会被杀死
And every soul who wishes you harm
will be struck down.
只要你的血脉里还流着我的血
Just as sure
as my blood runs in your veins,
你就会回到我身边
you will return to me.
尽管我们之间有矛盾，蕾贝卡
In spite of our differences,
Rebekah,
但把女儿交给你，我最放心
there is no one I would trust more
with my daughter's life.
要幸福，妹妹
Be happy, sister.
她会幸福的，尼克，我保证
She will be happy, Nik. I promise.
她叫什么名字？
What's her name?
希望
Hope.
她叫希望
Her name is Hope.
愿你安息
MAN: May you rest in peace.
那有什么意思？
WOMAN: What's the fun in that?
来吧，我们有许多事要做
Come along. We have much to do.
是的，母亲
Yes mother.
（艾丝塔 我们敬爱的母亲）
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）